Stealin' stones and breakin' bones.
Snatch is a crime, comedy film directed by Guy Ritchie.
Unscrupulous boxing promoters, violent bookies, a Russian gangster, incompetent amateur robbers,
and supposedly Jewish jewellers fight to track down a priceless stolen diamond.
Turkish, played by Jason Statham.
Brick Top, played by Alan Ford.
Tommy, played by Stephen Graham.
Mickey O'Neil, played by Brad Pitt.
Avi, played by Dennis Farina.
Vinny, played by Robbie Gee.
Snatch is a 2000 British crime comedy film written and directed by Guy Ritchie,
featuring an ensemble cast and set in the London criminal underworld.
The film contains two intertwined plots: one following the search for a stolen diamond, and the other focusing on a small-time boxing promoter
(Jason Statham) who becomes embroiled with a ruthless gangster (Alan Ford) willing to carry out severe and sadistic acts of violence.
The film shares themes and stylistic elements with Ritchie's first feature, Lock,
Stock and Two Smoking Barrels, and includes many of the same actors.
It is noted for its fast-paced editing, ensemble
storytelling, and dark comedic tone.
The film explores themes of robbery, trailer park, england, gypsy, gambling.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.